ZOE ELLEN POINTON

Two years design experience working within the Tech Industry. Graduated from the University of Winchester with a **First Class Honours**, in Digital Media Design. Looking to find a more challenging job in **UX/UI design**, with a team that I can both learn from and contribute to.

EXPERIENCE

TruDigital, Portsmouth — UX/UI Designer

APRIL 2018 - PRESENT

Formerly part of CDG. My role in the company was to design and build websites for our SME clients using WordPress. I also took a lead role in streamlining the design/development process for the 'affordable' website offering. Duties include; client meetings, creating user journeys, wireframes, style guides, design mockups, prototypes, building websites using WordPress and conducting focus groups.

CDG, Sunningdale — *Graduate Designer*

MAY 2017 - APRIL 2018

After completing my degree I started full time work at CDG as a Graduate Designer. With this came new challenges and greater responsibility, such as; involvement in client and sales meetings, preparing and conducting user focus groups and time management. As well as working on client projects, I also got the opportunity to work within product teams, creating and refining digital products using agile methodologies. Duties include; creating user journeys, wireframes, style guides, design mockups, prototypes, writing research reports, conducting focus groups, taking part in client meetings and creating email templates.

CDG, Sunningdale — *Digital Design Intern*

MAY 2016 - APRIL 2017

During my last year at university I got the opportunity to work within industry alongside my study. Working at CDG gave me valuable insight into the Tech Industry. It also allowed me to develop my design and problem solving skills and gain new experience working with clients in a professional environment. Duties include; designing icons, assisting in web development, designing web mockups and creating print collateral.

Thorpe Park Resort, Thorpe — *Entertainments Host*

APRIL 2015 - AUGUST 2015

Working as an entertainments host was my first official work experience. This opportunity helped me gain basic skills in customer service, problem solving, health & safety, and public speaking.

EDUCATION

The University of Winchester, Winchester — *BA Digital Media Design*

SEPTEMBER 2014 - MAY 2017

Graduated with a First Class Honours degree. During the course I learnt about a variety of different topics via lectures, writing reports and completing projects. Modules include; UX/UI design, web development, graphic design, animation, motion graphics, social media, agile and waterfall project management, business and research.

26 Harpesford Avenue, Virginia Water, Surrey GU25 4RD

(+44) 7935 408399

zoepointon123@gmail.com

SKILLS

Adobe Creative Suite

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, After Effects, Experience Design

Other Sketch, Invision, Agile

Technical HTML, CSS, Wordpress

Atlassian Jira, Confluence, Trello

AWARDS

Transmedia 2017 Pitch a Project Winner The
University of Winchester

CERTIFICATIONS

The Online Marketing Fundamentals Google

CHARITY WORK

Volunteer CAMEO Day Centres

Fundraising Sleeper Byte Night

PORTFOLIO

www.zoeellenpointon.com